<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://werealldoomed.com/rss.xml">
  <channel>
    <title>We're All Doomed!</title>
    <link>https://werealldoomed.com/rss.xml</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Singer woke up this morning</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/personal/singer_woke_morning</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Singer woke up this morning&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Thu, 11/29/2001 - 10:20&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/5" hreflang="en"&gt;Personal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Blind Willie McGee woke up this morning to find his woman had left him, his dog was dead, and he had gambled the rent away.

Yes, he woke up this morning to find his woman had left him, his dog was dead, and he had gambled the rent away.

"Yeah, man, it happens everyday, and I'm getting really sick of it" McGee said as he idly strummed a three-chord pattern on his guitar. "I go down to the crossroads, but that just makes things worse."

His friend Willie Brown says he's suggested that things might be different if Blind Willie would learn a fourth chord, but McGee prefers to spend his time tinkering in the shed, trying to get his mojo working.&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2001 16:20:19 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">26 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Danger of low-tar cigarettes surprises smokers</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/personal/danger_low_tar_cigarettes_surprises_smokers</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Danger of low-tar cigarettes surprises smokers&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Wed, 11/28/2001 - 11:41&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/5" hreflang="en"&gt;Personal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Smokers were dealt a surprising blow yesterday when the National Cancer Institute announced that low-tar cigarettes are unhealthy. They had been similarly shocked to learn in past years of the dangers associated with regular cigarettes.

"When I heard that smoking cigarettes might cause health problems, I switched from Chesterfield Kings to Merit Ultra Lights," said longtime smoker Brianna Jordan. "It was hard enough to see anything wrong with smoking regular cigarettes - who'd have expected that slightly reducing the most dangerous ingredient wouldn't help?"

Jordan is now switching to marijuana. "It's obviously the tobacco that's the problem, I can't believe there's anything inherently unhealthy about intentionally inhaling smoke," she said as she took a drag by the front door of her office building.&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2001 17:41:00 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">25 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Taliban surprisingly unpopular</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/political/taliban_surprisingly_unpopular</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Taliban surprisingly unpopular&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Tue, 11/20/2001 - 14:52&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/2" hreflang="en"&gt;Political&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Since the Northern Alliance rapidly overran most of Afghanistan last week, Afghan citizens have openly celebrated the Taliban's loss of control, shedding their burqas, shaving their beards, and playing music. Taliban officials have expressed amazement at their former subjects' lack of appreciation.

"We freed women from any concerns about work, education, or fashion, and protected them by brutally abusing any woman attempting to lift herself above her place, yet no one respects us. How can this be?" asked Taliban leader Mullah Mohammed Omar, from a cave near Kandahar. "We took away their music, movies, and television - what more could the people ask from a despotic government? While our armed soldiers were in every town enforcing our whims, no one complained - how were we to know there was no true loyalty to us?"

Asked about the foreign militants who appear to be the only people in Afghanistan now supporting the Taliban, Omar replied "We've gone to the trouble of importing vicious killers from throughout the region, and our own people don't appreciate our efforts. I don't know why we even bother trying any more."

Omar and his friend and colleague Osama bin Laden are currently working with their travel agent to find a nation which would welcome having its women treated as chattel, and all forms of joy prohibited. The task has proven surprisingly difficult.&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2001 20:52:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">24 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Real World preferred over real world</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/cultural/real_world_preferred_over_real_world</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Real World preferred over real world&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Wed, 11/14/2001 - 11:59&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/4" hreflang="en"&gt;Cultural&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Thousands of attractive, dysfunctional narcissists from 18 to 24 years old are descending on &lt;a href="http://www.bunim-murray.com/casting2001/index.html"&gt;open casting calls&lt;/a&gt; for MTV's The Real World, while snubbing the CNN version of the real world. Given the alternatives of cavorting with beautiful, horny people in a contrived living situation in Las Vegas, or dealing with the constant fear of death infiltrating the mail or falling from the sky, these young adults are making a clear choice for their preferred reality.

Among the hundreds of candidates lining Boston's Lansdowne Street today was Abbey Washington. "I saw what both worlds offered, and, like, duh!", she replied when asked about her choice. "Have you seen what people look like on CNN? Hair a mess, any old clothes just thrown on, half of them covered in dust and soot - I want to look fabulous when I'm on TV!"

CNN reported disappointment in the response to their own casting calls, which afforded auditioners the opportunity to spend their fifteen minutes of fame grieving family and friends. Producer James Adderley said "We thought offering frequent flier miles would help attract more candidates - clearly, though, MTV has out-marketed us in this demographic."&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 14 Nov 2001 17:59:14 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">23 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>FBI shocked to find pathetic loser behind anthrax attacks</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/political/fbi_shocked_find_pathetic_loser_behind_anthrax_attacks</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;FBI shocked to find pathetic loser behind anthrax attacks&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Sat, 11/10/2001 - 13:43&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/2" hreflang="en"&gt;Political&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;The FBI yesterday released a profile of the person suspected of sending anthrax-laden letters to several government and media organizations. Much to the investigators' surprise, the evidence suggests that this person is most likely a "pathetic loser".

"This really caught us by surprise", said a spokesman. "We usually expect the sort of person who commits publicity-seeking murders to be well-adjusted, articulate, and socially adept, and frequently described by their many friends and acquaintances as friendly and generous. Discovering that the perpetrator is most likely an antisocial troll with a persecution complex is a revelation to us."

In related news, Attorney General John Ashcroft asked Americans to be tolerant of their reclusive neighbors. "Loners are Americans too," he said, "and should be treated with the same respect as anyone else, regardless of whether they are computer geeks, senior citizens with herds of cats, or just the creepy guy next door."&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 10 Nov 2001 19:43:03 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">22 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Hell, Justice Department in antitrust pact</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/religious/hell_justice_department_antitrust_pact</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Hell, Justice Department in antitrust pact&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Sun, 11/04/2001 - 10:59&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/3" hreflang="en"&gt;Religious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;The Justice Department and Hell have agreed to a settlement in their protracted antitrust suit, Hell CEO Satan announced at a press conference Friday. Hell had been accused of leveraging the market dominance of its Hate and Greed product lines to control the various applications of evil.

Under the agreement, Hell will provide details of the inner workings of Hate and Greed to rival evil entities, allowing them to more easily integrate their own applications. Al-Qaeda, Aryan Nations, and Microsoft Corporation have already begun negotiating new licenses.

"While the settlement goes further than we might have wanted," Satan said, "we believe that settling this case now is the right thing to do to help worldwide evil move forward. We recognize that the success of our products has created concerns. This settlement enables Hell to continue innovating and pushing evil forward."&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 04 Nov 2001 16:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">21 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Horror characters face difficult times</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/cultural/horror_characters_face_difficult_times</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Horror characters face difficult times&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Tue, 10/30/2001 - 11:43&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/4" hreflang="en"&gt;Cultural&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;The hirsute drinker snubbed out his cigarette on the bar as closing time approached. "I should be out there right now," he complained, "but it's pointless." From the vicinity of a Bud Light bottle suspended over the next stool came "Yeah, now the only way I could get a rise out of people would be to toss some flour in the air. I'm as patriotic as the next American, man, I'm not going to exploit things that way."

The laments of the Wolfman and the Invisible Man are all too common this Halloween, as the realities of the modern world have driven down demand for traditional sources of fear. Generally, fiends and monsters make enough income from personal appearances in October to fund their depravations for the next year, but this year many of them may find themselves on the unemployment rolls.

Count Dracula is suffering more than most. "What most people don't understand," he says, "is that the main nutritional value I get from sucking people's blood is the adrenalin - if they're not frightened when I bite, it's just empty calories". He declined to say what he is doing to pay for his weekly adrenalin injections at the local health clinic, saying "It's just too humiliating", but investigation by We're All Doomed has turned up invoices in his name for "Modeling Services" at General Mills' advertising agency, in a folder related to the upcoming redesign of their Count Chocula cereal boxes.&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 30 Oct 2001 17:43:20 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">20 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Sales of depressing music down</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/cultural/sales_depressing_music_down</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Sales of depressing music down&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Fri, 10/26/2001 - 15:35&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/4" hreflang="en"&gt;Cultural&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;The band Anthrax may have been only joking about changing their name to Basket Full of Puppies, but they just might be on to something - the market for depressed and angry music has declined to its lowest level in recording history.

Tower Records reports that sales of metal have declined 75%, industrial music is down 90%, and not a single Goth CD has been sold since September 11 (the spokesman declined to comment on when the last Goth sale before September 11 occurred).

Noted psychologist James Ervin explains "Well, the primary market for this music has always been adolescents with comfortable middle- and upper-class lives - i.e., those who lack any genuine reasons to be depressed and angry, other than simply being adolescents. Now that the real world is providing them with their necessary minimum daily requirement of angst, they no longer need to seek it through music."

In related news, various volumes of the 70's compilation series "Have a Nice Day", featuring such harmless songs as "Brand New Key" and "Afternoon Delight", have taken 8 of the top 10 slots on the Billboard charts.&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2001 20:35:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">19 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>The sky is falling</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/environmental/sky_falling</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;The sky is falling&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Thu, 10/25/2001 - 22:04&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/1" hreflang="en"&gt;Environmental&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;The Public Agency for Nervous Imperiled Citizens announced today that the sky is falling. Agency director C. Little reported "Measurements show that an average of one foot a week has been lost in the last month. People are advised to hoard oxygen and sunlight. An evacuation plan for the Rocky Mountain states is being developed. Tall people may wish to seek height reduction surgery."

Projections show that at the current rate of decline, the sky will touch the highest mountains in the world in approximately 14,000 years. "You can't be too careful", said Little.&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Oct 2001 03:04:54 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">18 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Hell reports third quarter results</title>
  <link>https://werealldoomed.com/religious/hell_reports_third_quarter_results</link>
  <description>&lt;span class="field field--name-title field--type-string field--label-hidden"&gt;Hell reports third quarter results&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-uid field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;mike&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class="field field--name-created field--type-created field--label-hidden"&gt;Tue, 10/23/2001 - 12:05&lt;/span&gt;

      &lt;div class="field field--name-topics field--type-entity-reference field--label-hidden field__items"&gt;
              &lt;div class="field__item"&gt;&lt;a href="https://werealldoomed.com/taxonomy/term/3" hreflang="en"&gt;Religious&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
          &lt;/div&gt;
  
            &lt;div class="clearfix text-formatted field field--name-body field--type-text-with-summary field--label-hidden field__item"&gt;Hell's quarterly report for the third quarter of 2001 was released today, reporting earnings well beyond analysts' projections.

"While there was much fanfare over the 19 souls who volunteered for the first ring of the seventh circle of Hell on September 11," stated Satan, CEO and president of Hell, "the long-term results are expected to be even more profitable. Suspicion and paranoia are sharply up, which will inevitably drive sales of hate and violence for at least the next two quarters. Fear has always been our strongest marketing tool, and the climate is ideal right now for our most aggressive campaign in sixty years."

Analysts agreed that Satan's marketing analysis was likely to be correct in the near future, but caution consumers that Hell's products have never been shown to be satisfying in the long run. Consumer Reports said in their statement "Customers who buy into Hell's hate product line often find the products blowing up in their faces - we give them a 'Not Recommended'."&lt;/div&gt;
      </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2001 17:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>mike</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="false">17 at https://werealldoomed.com</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>
